<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title/><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/</link><description>Recent content on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About Me</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/home/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/home/about/</guid><description>👋 Hello! I&amp;rsquo;m Chloe Abrasada. I actually have a second name that I don&amp;rsquo;t use for branding purposes (jkjk). I&amp;rsquo;m a productivity nerd 👩‍🏫, web lurker 💻, and design enthusiast 🎨.
📚 I&amp;rsquo;m an incoming third year student in UP Manila studying Occupational Therapy. Outside school, I part time as a designer and volunteer in NGOs related to my cause. 🍃
🔗 Links I publish my works here at my portfolio and Behance.</description></item><item><title>Active Listening</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/active-listening/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/active-listening/</guid><description>Tags: #permanent-notes Relevant Notes mental-health Notes Active listening involves consciously paying attention to who you&amp;rsquo;re listening to. The following are theskills involved in active listening: Reflection Labelling emotions Asking questions Empathy Lived experienced Identify strengths It involves mindfulness. and Self-awareness is important. You should be aware of your listening filters and personal thoughts. It is also important that you show that you&amp;rsquo;re listening.</description></item><item><title>Activism</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/activism/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/activism/</guid><description> Faux activism</description></item><item><title>Advocacy burnout</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/advocacy-burnout/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/advocacy-burnout/</guid><description>Tags: #permanent-notes Relevant Notes mental-health References LINK IN REFIND: On advocacy by Chloe Abrasada (chloe-abrasada) – Refind How to keep changing the world when you&amp;rsquo;re burning out - makesense Philippines Advocacy Burnout is Real - Girls' Globe How To Avoid Burnout for Sustainable Advocacy How Advocates for Inclusion Keep from Burning Out Breaking the burnout in advocacy | University of Technology Sydney How I (Try to) Avoid Advocacy Burnout | Cancer.</description></item><item><title>Advocacy MOC</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/advocacy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/advocacy/</guid><description> Environmental Education MOC Concepts Advocacy burnout</description></item><item><title>Art is political</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/art-political/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/art-political/</guid><description> Tags: #to-digest Relevant Notes Reads &amp;ldquo;Malakas at Maganda&amp;rdquo; as propaganda: Deceitful art during Martial Law - NOLISOLI</description></item><item><title>Art of questioning in UX design</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/art-of-questioning/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/art-of-questioning/</guid><description>Tags: #to-digest Relevant Notes learning-thinking-communicating ethics-in-tech #come-back Notes Highlights 59 Questions for Mindful UX Design — This Too Shall Grow 1 Exploratory questions ==What would you dislike about being a user of this product?== What’s the worst scenario that could happen because of this product? Are you OK with your loved ones knowing you worked on this? Are you OK with the users knowing you worked on this?</description></item><item><title>Availability bias</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/availability-bias/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/availability-bias/</guid><description>Tags: #permanent-notes Relevant Notes Notes Believing what&amp;rsquo;s convenient Believing what we connect most to ourself Highlights Availability bias is the tendency to rely on information that’s readily available, instead of what’s actually more relevant to the situation. In the context of workplace relationships, this often leads us to connect other people’s behavior to ourselves, because those are the experiences that are already occupying our mental space.</description></item><item><title>Avoid being reactive</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/avoid-being-reactive/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/avoid-being-reactive/</guid><description> Tags: #permanent-notes
Relevant Notes
Let go of things that are outside of your control For reflection “You must stop blaming God, and not blame any person. You must completely control your desire and shift your avoidance to what lies within your reasoned choice. You must no longer feel anger, resentment, envy, or regret.”—EPICTETUS, DISCOURSES, 3.22.1</description></item><item><title>Behavioral segmentation</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/behavioral-segmentation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/behavioral-segmentation/</guid><description>Tags: #permanent-notes Relevant Notes ux-design Notes Highlights Everything You Need to Know About Behavioral Segmentation [+ Examples] 1 Behavioral segmentation is the process of grouping customers into categories based on their behaviors or actions involving your business. This allows you to more effectively target and market to them. Behavioral Segmentation Variables The behavioral segmentation variables that you need to consider while working on the categorization of your audiences include: Sought-after product/service benefits of your audience members.</description></item><item><title>Biases</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/biases/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/biases/</guid><description> Confirmation bias Availability bias</description></item><item><title>Blogs</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/blogs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/blogs/</guid><description>Tags: #repository
Jon Brooks</description></item><item><title>Books</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/books/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/books/</guid><description> Ikigai by Francesc Miralles and Hector Garcia Atomic Habits by James Clear</description></item><item><title>Brand 99 Designs</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/brand-99-designs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/brand-99-designs/</guid><description> Reference: Vistaprint Special Branding Bundle Highlights Day 1: Brand basics Day 2: Strategy Day 3: Key elements Day 4: Logos Day 5: Touchpoints Day 6: Social Day 7: Style guides</description></item><item><title>Branding experience</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/branding-experience/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/branding-experience/</guid><description>Tags: #permanent-notes Relevant Notes ux-design Notes What is branding experience Brand experience encompasses subjective consumer responses in the form of sensations, feelings, thoughts, and reactions responses in response to brand-related stimuli. They are part of a brand&amp;rsquo;s design by identity, packaging, communications, and environments. Importance Good brand experience connects more with the audience in a way that it sticks with them more and facilitates deeper connections.</description></item><item><title>Branding MOC</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/branding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/branding/</guid><description> Branding experience Learning Programs Brand by 99design</description></item><item><title>Building this Website</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/home/building-this-website/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/home/building-this-website/</guid><description>Oldest to latest 07/26/2021 Quartz Set-up 07/27/2021 Site actually FINALLY up lol struggled through that What I didn&amp;rsquo;t know before this lol Wikilinks don&amp;rsquo;t work on Github Pages Doesn&amp;rsquo;t support spaces 07/29/2021 Fixed backlinks What I didn&amp;rsquo;t know before this There was an error in my config.toml 07/29/2021 Change color of page 07/31/2021 Add &amp;ldquo;Let&amp;rsquo;s go back&amp;rdquo; on 404 How to make an HTML back link 08/01/2021 Add date late updated at footer Last modified date of a file on a website 08/01/2021 Add changelog at footer Obsidian Vault changelog plug-in What I didn&amp;rsquo;t know before this Won&amp;rsquo;t really work without frontmatter 08/02/2021 Add option to remove TOC 08/03/2021 Add arrow to external links Superscript in CSS only?</description></item><item><title>Burnout</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/burnout/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/burnout/</guid><description>Tags: Relevant Notes yerkes-dodson-law References Episode 3: Burnout in Online Classes - Psych Speaks: A Mental Health Podcast Series | Podcast on Spotify Notes Burnout has three different dimensions: exhaustion, cynism (apathy &amp;amp; detachment from work), and lack of professional efficacy (a drop in your performance). Burnout is not something that should be normalized. Compared to stress , burnout does not have any more motivation involved.</description></item><item><title>Burnout is an organizational issue</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/burnout-organizational-issue/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/burnout-organizational-issue/</guid><description>Tags: Relevant Notes Reference The Burnout Conversation Is A Corporate Tool To Turn Your Suffering Into Marketing - by Ed Z - Ed Zitron&amp;rsquo;s Where&amp;rsquo;s Your Ed At Notes The reason why people burnout in companies is not solely about amount of workload. Some examples are unending workstream, unjust compenstation, etc. Burnout within organization is not something that can be solved through &amp;ldquo;days-off&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;giving people self-care apps&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Buyer personas</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/buyer-personas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/buyer-personas/</guid><description> Tags:#i #in-progress/garden Relevant Notes Sources Buyer Persona Template &amp;amp; Persona Examples - Milanote Notes Highlights</description></item><item><title>Candidate red flags</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/candidate-red-flags/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/candidate-red-flags/</guid><description> Tags: #permanent-notes Relevant Notes getting-hired interviews Notes 1 Arriving late without update Rude Dodge question about failures Want to leave current job because they are bored Asks questions for the sake of asking questions Highlights LinkedIn Talent Solutions 15 Interview Productivity Hacks &amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;</description></item><item><title>Career Advice MOC</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/career-advice/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/career-advice/</guid><description> Your career is not a life sentence On choosing your commitments When to quit a job? Career growth tracking Your job is not worth your mental health Work ethics</description></item><item><title>Career growth trackingg</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/growth-tracking/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/growth-tracking/</guid><description> Tags: #come-back Relevant Notes Notes Highlights Tooling How I use FigJam to track my career growth | by Justine Win | Aug, 2021 | Justine Win Stories Figma</description></item><item><title>Case studies in UX design</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/case-study/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/case-study/</guid><description>Tags: #permanent-notes Relevant Notes Notes Highlights Sahil Bishnoi on LinkedIn 1 What was the project goal? Set up the context by explaining the problem / goal that your client or team is trying to achieve. What was your research process? How did you consider to explore this problem initially? Were there any changes to the process later on? What main insights research gave you? What insight were crucial further shaped or informed your design?</description></item><item><title>Changelog</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/changelog/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/changelog/</guid><description> 2021-08-24 at 17h40 · [[press-release]] 2021-08-24 at 17h18 · [[digital-marketing]] 2021-08-23 at 02h52 · [[yerkes-dodson-law]] 2021-08-23 at 02h49 · [[burnout]] 2021-08-23 at 02h40 · [[mental-health]] 2021-08-23 at 02h33 · [[psychology]] 2021-08-23 at 02h23 · [[interplays]] 2021-08-22 at 13h22 · [[about]] 2021-08-22 at 13h12 · [[burnout-organizational-issue]] 2021-08-22 at 13h09 · [[general-interview-questions]] 2021-08-22 at 13h08 · [[work-culture]] 2021-08-21 at 10h50 · [[seo-writing]] 2021-08-21 at 10h48 · [[seo]] 2021-08-20 at 12h45 · [[marketing-getting-hired]] 2021-08-20 at 12h43 · [[marketing]] 2021-08-20 at 12h41 · [[getting-hired]] 2021-08-20 at 03h43 · [[writing-projects]] 2021-08-19 at 19h41 · [[strategic-marketing-plan]] 2021-08-19 at 18h31 · [[marketing-case-study-notes]] 2021-08-19 at 03h15 · [[writing-for-marketers]]</description></item><item><title>Check your privilege</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/privilege/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/privilege/</guid><description>Tags: Relevant Notes life-advice relating Notes Quotes “Some people are sharp and others dull; some are raised in a better environment, others in worse, the latter, having inferior habits and nurture, will require more by way of proof and careful instruction to master these teachings and to be formed by them—in the same way that bodies in a bad state must be given a great deal of care when perfect health is sought.</description></item><item><title>Chloe's Corner</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/home/corner/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/home/corner/</guid><description> Note: #in-progress/garden
Tooling To Read Things at the top of my ahead I want to learn about #come-back Organization structures Authenticity Project roadmapping 08112021 2~ weeks with Obsidian! The pink ones are my private notes while the blue ones are the ones in this garden! ✌️</description></item><item><title>choose-perspective</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/choose-perspective/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/choose-perspective/</guid><description> Tags: Relevant Notes Notes Take a perspective that empowers you personally. Quotes and Insights &amp;ldquo;Different meanings can be assigned to the same events. Look for evidence of how the world is encouraging you, and you will find it. Look for evidence of how the world is burdening you, and you will find it. Choose an explanation that empowers you.&amp;quot;–James Clear (related to: stoicism ) Highlights</description></item><item><title>Circular Economy</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/circular-economy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/circular-economy/</guid><description>Tags: #to-digest Relevant Notes Notes Highlights How Circular is the Circular Economy? - Local Futures 1
In the circular economy, resources would be continually re-used, meaning that there would be no more mining activity or waste production. The stress is on recycling, made possible by designing products so that they can easily be taken apart.
Several scientific studies (see references) describe the concept as an “idealised vision”, a “mix of various ideas from different domains”, or a “vague idea based on pseudo-scientific concepts”.</description></item><item><title>Collective Effervesence</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/collective-effervesence/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/collective-effervesence/</guid><description>Tags: #to-digest Relevant Notes notes/emotions-contagious Notes Highlights We find our greatest bliss in moments of collective effervescence. It’s a concept coined in the early 20th century by the pioneering sociologist Émile Durkheim to describe the sense of energy and harmony people feel when they come together in a group around a shared purpose. Collective effervescence is the synchrony you feel when you slide into rhythm with strangers on a dance floor, colleagues in a brainstorming session, cousins at a religious service or teammates on a soccer field.</description></item><item><title>collector-fallacy</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/collector-fallacy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/collector-fallacy/</guid><description>Tags: #permanent-notes Relevant Notes Notes Fallacy: As you collect, your knowledge grows But what actually happens is that you don&amp;rsquo;t process and digest these notes Although a lengthy process, take time to convert these notes into ones you actually learn, know, and digest&amp;ndash;you don&amp;rsquo;t learn just by highlighting Highlights The Collector’s Fallacy • Zettelkasten Method The worst we could do is to pile up copies until the stack grows intimidatingly high, until it becomes unmanageable.</description></item><item><title>Confirmation Bias</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/confirmation-bias/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/confirmation-bias/</guid><description>Tags: #in-progress/garden #to-digest Relevant Notes Notes Highlights On the other hand, confirmation bias is at play when you seek out information that fits in with how you already see the world. Confirmation bias can seriously harm your relationships, especially if you have any negative associations with your employer, workplace, or anyone on your team.1 How Teams Can Be More Supportive With Help From Hanlon’s Razor &amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;</description></item><item><title>Creatives MOC</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/creatives/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/creatives/</guid><description> Design MOC Branding MOC</description></item><item><title>critiquing-design</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/critiquing-design/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/critiquing-design/</guid><description>Tags: #to-digest Relevant Notes Notes Highlights Julie Zhuo on Twitter: &amp;ldquo;Everyone has an opinion on design. There&amp;rsquo;s always an immediate gut reaction: &amp;ldquo;Ooh, I love this!&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Meh.&amp;rdquo; But how do you go beyond that to honing your skills of giving helpful, actionable feedback? Here are the 7 questions I run through when critiquing a product&amp;rsquo;s design 👇&amp;rdquo; / Twitter What is the user journey to get here?</description></item><item><title>Curated - Interviews Questions for Companies (Internships/Jobs)</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/interviews-companies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/interviews-companies/</guid><description>Tags: #personal-learnings #permanent-notes Relevant Notes general-interview-questions notes/getting-hired Common Questions Tell me about yourself. Why do you want this position? What do you about our company? What do you expect from the job? Why will you be a good for for XYZ? What are your strengths? What are your weaknesses? Tell me about a time you made a mistake. What will you bring to the table?</description></item><item><title>Curated - Interviews Questions for Leadership in Organizations</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/interviews-org/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/interviews-org/</guid><description>Tags: #personal-learnings #permanent-notes Relevant Notes general-interview-questions notes/getting-hired Common Questions Tell me about yourself. Why do you want this position? Are you aware of XYZ and its projects? How would you encourage members to join projects/ events? Do you have any projects in mind for the organization? What are your past relevant experience? What will you bring? Tell me about a time you demonstrated leadership skills.</description></item><item><title>customer-relationship-management</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/customer-relationship-management/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/customer-relationship-management/</guid><description> Tags: #come-back #in-progress/garden Relevant Notes Sources CRM Template-Salesforce Notes Highlights</description></item><item><title>Cybersecurity</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/cybersecurity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/cybersecurity/</guid><description>Cool Reads Apple explains how iPhones will scan photos for child-sexual-abuse images | Ars Technica Clubhouse: The Hot New Social Network Has Big Privacy Problems Tooling Have I Been Pwned: Check if your email has been compromised in a data breach</description></item><item><title>Design is political x Decolonizing design</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/decolonizing-design/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/decolonizing-design/</guid><description>Tags: #permanent-notes Relevant Notes Notes Western ideologies have shaped our concepts of &amp;ldquo;preferable design&amp;rdquo;. Anything outside these Western preferences are seen as different or inferior. We should remove the distinction of art and craft.1 The concept of a difference between art and craft reflect classist distinctions from the West. Highlights What Does It Mean to Decolonize Design? 2
“Colonization” is rooted in indigenous peoples’ experiences of oppression—specifically, the seizure of native resources, as well as the embedding of Western ideology into society The work designers make is inspired by taste, and taste is often derived from what we’re exposed to during our upbringing.</description></item><item><title>Design MOC</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/design/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/design/</guid><description> Visual design Design is political x Decolonizing design Design teams Leadership in design Cool Tools Where to learn Designing for accesibility Designing for inclusivity Art is political</description></item><item><title>Design sources</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/design-sources/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/design-sources/</guid><description> Tags: #repository Relevant Notes design-tools-sources General The Best Curated Resources For Designer – Resourcesfordesigner.com</description></item><item><title>Design Teams</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/design-teams/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/design-teams/</guid><description>Tags: #permanent-notes Relevant Notes leadership in design work-culture Notes How to build a design team Work cultures &amp;amp; environments are different–we hire people that would complement the team. The filtering process is important as every member contributes to the overall flow of the team The baseline process involves asking two questions: How well will this person work with the team culture?</description></item><item><title>Design Tools &amp; Sources</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/design-tools-sources/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/design-tools-sources/</guid><description> Tags: #repository Relevant Notes ux-tools tooling Tools General Photopea InDesign Spline - Design tool for 3D web experiences blender.org - Home of the Blender project - Free and Open 3D Creation Software Presentations Storydoc: Make your company shine. Staying Inspired Muzli 2 - Stay Inspired Material Sources Icons Feather – Simply beautiful open source icons Icons - Google Fonts Free Vector Icons and Stickers - PNG, SVG, EPS, PSD and CSS Noun Project: Free Icons &amp;amp; Stock Photos for Everything Super — Icons 🏠 Icons - UX Library Illustrations Illustrations | unDraw Blush: Illustrations for everyone DrawKit - Beautiful vector illustrations 🎄 Illustrations - UX Library Stock Photos Beautiful Free Images &amp;amp; Pictures | Unsplash Free Stock Photos · Pexels Royalty Free HD Stock Photos and Images - Gratisography picjumbo: Free Stock Photos</description></item><item><title>Digital Marketing MOC</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/digital-marketing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/digital-marketing/</guid><description>Types Search engine optimization Affiliate marketing Display advertising Email marketing Social media or influence marketing Content marketing Remarketing Pragmatic marketing Mobile marketing PPC Press release</description></item><item><title>Don't be afraid of failure</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/afraid-failure/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/afraid-failure/</guid><description> Tags: #extra-push #permanent-notes Relevant Notes career-advice feedback Notes Your good ideas are hidden under the bad ones Your first 50 attempts will be terrible, so go ahead and use them up Highlights</description></item><item><title>Education</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/education/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/education/</guid><description>MOCs Research MOC Concepts How should we teach?</description></item><item><title>Emotions are contagious</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/emotions-contagious/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/emotions-contagious/</guid><description>Tags: #permanent-notes Relevant Notes collective-effervesence Notes You feel the emotions around the people around you. Some examples of these are collective anxiety, Zoom fatigue, etc. Highlights When the pandemic began in 2020, the first negative emotion to spread was fear. Waves of panic crashed through communities, compelling people to purify packages and hoard hand sanitizer. As too many people lost loved ones, too many others lost jobs and everyone lost some semblance of normal life.</description></item><item><title>Empathy</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/empathy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/empathy/</guid><description> We are unkind because we our empathy is limited Empathy is in admitting that we don&amp;rsquo;t understand</description></item><item><title>Environmental Education MOC</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/environmental-educ/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/environmental-educ/</guid><description> Environmental justice Eco-theories
Circular economy Plenitude Ecomodernism</description></item><item><title>Ethics</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/ethics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/ethics/</guid><description> Related to: Ethics in tech Ethics activities</description></item><item><title>Ethics Activities</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/ethics-activities/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/ethics-activities/</guid><description> Ethics Litmus Tests PDF Version</description></item><item><title>Facilitation MOC</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/facilitation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/facilitation/</guid><description> No uploaded notes yet! Still building. 👷‍♀️</description></item><item><title>Faux Activism</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/faux-activism/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/faux-activism/</guid><description> Tags: #in-progress/garden #read-queue Sources How social justice slideshows made by activists took over Instagram - Vox to-read</description></item><item><title>Feedback</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/feedback/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/feedback/</guid><description>Tags: #might-publish #personal-learnings Related to: No to micromanaging life-advice I really value the importance of giving feedback. Our words are too powerful to impart things callously. I&amp;rsquo;ve seen people give feedback differently, and I think there&amp;rsquo;s no super perfect formula into giving it because people are so unpredictable and subjective. I adjust my approach, but what I always seek to maintain is to relay feedback in a constructive manner that helps a person move forward concretely.</description></item><item><title>Feminism MOC</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/feminism/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/feminism/</guid><description> Workplace equity</description></item><item><title>Focus on your user and everything else will follow</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/focus-on-user/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/focus-on-user/</guid><description> Tags: #to-digest Relevant Notes human-centric design Notes Highlights If you do a quick search to understand the ROI (return on investment) of focusing on your users, you’ll quickly learn that customer-focused companies can be 60% more profitable than non-customer-focused companies.1 Survey Design Guide: Process, Principles, and Questions | Maze &amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;</description></item><item><title>General interview questions and how to answer</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/general-interview-questions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/general-interview-questions/</guid><description>Tags: #permanent-notes #personal-learnings Relevant Notes career-advice notes/skills/hr/getting-hired ty-note what-do-recruiters-want General Techniques STAR Method SITUATION: Give the interviewer context by describing the situation. TASK: What did you need to do? ACTION: What were your specific actions? RESULT: What was the end result? What did you learn? How did it affect others? Elevator Pitch Problem-Solution-Benefit1 Answer should contain: A problem you faced, Your solution, The benefit to your employer.</description></item><item><title>Getting hired</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/getting-hired/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/getting-hired/</guid><description> Interviews What do recruiters want? Candidate red flags Marketing getting hired</description></item><item><title>Good work ethics in remote work</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/good-work-ethics-remote-work/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/good-work-ethics-remote-work/</guid><description> Tags: #permanent-notes Relevant Notes Notes Set meetings only with agendas. Communicate: What the meeting is about &amp;amp; what a person&amp;rsquo;s role would be in the meeting. (related to: How to facilitate effective meetings ) Don&amp;rsquo;t presume people are always available. Set the conversation consistently. Turn on your camera. Highlights Sources 5 Habits of Highly Ineffective Remote Workers | Better Programming</description></item><item><title>Hanlon's Razor</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/hanlon/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/hanlon/</guid><description>Tags: #permanent-notes Relevant Notes design-teams leadership positive-leadership kindness mental-models biases Notes “Never attribute to malice or stupidity that which can be explained by moderately rational individuals following incentives in a complex system of interactions.” You should assume the best in people. Highlights How Teams Can Be More Supportive With Help From Hanlon’s Razor 1 “Never attribute to malice or stupidity that which can be explained by moderately rational individuals following incentives in a complex system of interactions.</description></item><item><title>How I give feedback</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/projects/how-i-give-feedback/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/projects/how-i-give-feedback/</guid><description>Date: 08072021 Iteration of feedback Tags: #in-progress/garden #projects #personal-learnings Related to: positive-leadership Pop-up ideas Specific, digestible, action-oriented Outline Paper I&amp;rsquo;ve worked with multiple diverse teams over the past years–from group of friends, classmates, bunch of strangers, to workplace teams. Along with the diversity of the teams also comes different work and communicatino dynamics, so you never know what to expect with each team.</description></item><item><title>How should we teach?</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/how-should-we-teach/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/how-should-we-teach/</guid><description> Tags: Relevant Notes Notes Quotes &amp;ldquo;The teacher is of course an artist, but being an artist does not mean that he or she can make the profile, can shape the students. What the educator does in teaching is to make it possible for the students to become themselves.&amp;rdquo; -Paulo Freire Highlights</description></item><item><title>How to be a better writer</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/how-to-be-a-better-writer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/how-to-be-a-better-writer/</guid><description> How to write better sentences</description></item><item><title>How to Be Stoic</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/how-to/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/how-to/</guid><description>Still finding where I got these!
Tags: #philosophy #to-digest Relevant Notes What to answer to mamamatay rin tayong lahat Notes Highlights Dichotomy of Control “The chief task in life is simply this: to identify and separate matters so that I can say clearly to myself which are externals not under my control, and which have to do with the choices I actually control. Where then do I look for good and evil?</description></item><item><title>How to Change Your Life</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/change-life/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/change-life/</guid><description>Tags: #extra-push #to-digest Relevant Notes Notes Highlights Three Steps To Transform Your Life1
From a YT Comment
Step 1. Laser focus on what you want and only what you want. Don&amp;rsquo;t talk yourself or allow yourself to be talked out of your desire. Write it down. Don&amp;rsquo;t let yourself get distracted. Step 2. Question what you consciously and unconsciously believe about your desire. Limiting beliefs prevent us from getting what we desire.</description></item><item><title>How to write better sentences</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/write-better-sentences/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/write-better-sentences/</guid><description>Tags: #permanent-notes Relevant Notes Notes Be creative in writing. Play with the emotions of the readers such as fear, surprise, or their senses. There are different techniques you can try: Add in a sensory flair to you writing. Keenly describe the scenario with different sentences. You can break some writing rules in a sentence. Build tension and suspense. You can use one-liners or intense cliffhangers. You can make writing that severely precise in quick succession.</description></item><item><title>how-to-apologzize</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/how-to-apologize/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/how-to-apologize/</guid><description>Tags: Relevant Notes leadership learning-thinking-communicating Notes Apologizing to a colleague Make it personal: Private &amp;gt; public Just admit the mistake, don&amp;rsquo;t try to defend yourself/ make yourself look better Formula Admit the mistake Connect with emotion Offer a solution Highlights Apologies are never easy – especially in the workplace 1 “I note that the event took place in front of other people, but I think the person who messed up should first offer a private apology because an apology should focus on the needs of the aggrieved person, and that person might not want a public apology.</description></item><item><title>Human Resources MOC</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/hr/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/hr/</guid><description> Career Advice MOC Interviews General - Interview questions and how to answer them Curated - Interviews Questions for Leadership in Organizations Curated - Interviews Questions for Companies (Internships/Jobs) Work culture Work structures Getting hired Workplace communication Work ethics</description></item><item><title>Ikigai</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/ikigai/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/ikigai/</guid><description> Tags: #in-progress Relevant Notes Insights &amp;ldquo;We don’t create the meaning of our life, as Sartre claimed—we discover it. We each have a unique reason for being, which can be adjusted or transformed many times over the years.&amp;rdquo; Ikigai #pondering I&amp;rsquo;m still thinking about if I agree with this. I think that you can create and define your purpose in life, not solely discover it. Still thinking&amp;hellip; Notes Highlights</description></item><item><title>InDesign</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/indesign/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/indesign/</guid><description>Templates Old Style Newspaper Template - StockInDesign Top 8 Best Free InDesign Templates Sites - Mockups by Carlos Viloria</description></item><item><title>Interplays of Mathematics and Classism – Math 10 2021 Capstone</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/projects/interplays/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/projects/interplays/</guid><description>Note: Not final paper uploaded here. This is a collection of somerandom thought processes, brainstorm, and pre-readings.
What my space looks like when writing Research Document PH&amp;rsquo;s Grade 4 students lowest in math, science around the world &amp;ndash; int&amp;rsquo;l study | Inquirer News ==Only one percent reached the high benchmark==, meaning, “students can apply conceptual understanding to solve problems.” In 2019, Programme for International Student Assessment (Pisa) by the Organization for Economic Cooperation and Development (OECD) found that ==Filipinos fared worst among 79 countries in reading literacy and second-lowest in both mathematical and scientific literacy.</description></item><item><title>Interviews</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/interviews/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/interviews/</guid><description> Interview questions and how to answer them Curated - Interviews Questions for Leadership in Organizations Curated - Interviews Questions for Companies (Internships/Jobs)</description></item><item><title>Kindness MOC</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/kindness/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/kindness/</guid><description> On relating to others Kindness and empathy Sharing appreciation Active listening Unspoken rules of kindness Hanlon&amp;rsquo;s razor Quotes Always be a little kinder than necessary</description></item><item><title>Launch marketing</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/launch-marketing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/launch-marketing/</guid><description> Tags: #in-progress/garden Relevant Notes Sources Betterment&amp;rsquo;s Launch Marketing Template Notes Highlights</description></item><item><title>Leadership MOC</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/leadership/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/leadership/</guid><description> Feedback Positive Leadership No to micromanaging Leadership in design How to facilitate effective meetings</description></item><item><title>Learning in public</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/learning-in-public/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/learning-in-public/</guid><description> Tags: Relevant Notes Notes Highlights Learn In Public: The fastest way to learn It&amp;rsquo;s not about reaching as many people as possible with your content Try your best to be right, but don&amp;rsquo;t worry when you&amp;rsquo;re wrong Solicit feedback Teaching is the best way to learn</description></item><item><title>Learning MOC</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/learning/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/learning/</guid><description> Lessen distractions</description></item><item><title>Learning, Thinking, &amp; Communicating MOC</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/learning-thinking-communicating/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/learning-thinking-communicating/</guid><description>MOCs Learning MOC Concepts Systems thinking Mental Models Second Brain Visual Thinking 5 Whys Public speaking Socratic method Hanlon&amp;rsquo;s razor Sources Kinopio to-read Use these visual thinking tools to explore, clarify, and communicate your ideas. | by Erin Rufledt Hunter | Luminary Lab | Medium ]</description></item><item><title>lessen-distractions</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/lessen-distractions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/lessen-distractions/</guid><description> Tags: #in-progress/garden Relevant Notes Systems thinking Notes Quotes On the internet, your rate of learning is not limited by your access to information, but by your ability to ignore the distractions. — David Perell Highlights</description></item><item><title>Life Advice MOC</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/life-advice/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/life-advice/</guid><description>Content Career Advice MOC Work ethics What to answer to mamamatay din tayong lahat How to change your life Choose your perspective Check your privilege Vulnerability Start with why–Golden Circle Don&amp;rsquo;t be afraid of failure Words &amp;amp; Quotes On Identity &amp;ldquo;Do not define me by circumstance, define me by my intention.</description></item><item><title>Make research accessible to the public</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/distilled-research-ecosystem/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/distilled-research-ecosystem/</guid><description>Tags: #permanent-notes Relevant Notes Notes We often glorify complex and hard-to-understand articles. However, this idea that the &amp;ldquo;climb should be hard&amp;rdquo; is not progress, we are instead putting on research debt. Research debt can come in the form of poor exposition, undigested ideas, bad abstractations and notation, and noise. When faced with these, people have to exert interpretative labor which varies depending on the material presented. We must move forward into research distillation .</description></item><item><title>Marketing analytics</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/marketing-analytics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/marketing-analytics/</guid><description>Tags: Relevant Notes Notes Literature Notes #3: Neil &amp;amp; Eric&amp;rsquo;s Favorite Marketing Tools - Marketing School - Digital Marketing and Online Marketing Tips | Podcast on Spotify 1 Analytics You need at least 6 months to generate quality organic traffic What works for Facebook does not work for organic == #come-back Google search console AHREFS Highlights backlinks, backlinks lost, and links of competitors Know about what your competitors are ranking for SEMRush Crazy egg Hellobar #3: Neil &amp;amp; Eric&amp;rsquo;s Favorite Marketing Tools - Marketing School - Digital Marketing and Online Marketing Tips | Podcast on Spotify &amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;</description></item><item><title>Marketing campaign tracking</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/marketing-campaign-tracking/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/marketing-campaign-tracking/</guid><description> Tags: #come-back Relevant Notes Sources Marketing Campaign Tracking Template Notes Highlights</description></item><item><title>Marketing campaigns</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/marketing-campaigns/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/marketing-campaigns/</guid><description> Marketing campaign tracking</description></item><item><title>Marketing case study notes</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/marketing-case-study-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/marketing-case-study-notes/</guid><description>Note: Convert the permanent notes in key takeaways to readable permanent notes
How I&amp;rsquo;d Grow Plausible by Zero to Marketing Key takeaways On SEO &amp;amp; selling points - Frame your value proposition based on what users find most appealing (via looking at testimonial) and search engine analytics On content - Choose relevant blog posts with &amp;ldquo;selling names&amp;rdquo; that would direct search On social media - Pick your platforms depending on your customer characteristics On strategies - Explore referral programs Highlights free plan with a referral program Twitter because it’s where their potential customers hang out All of them should be aimed at Plausible’s audience of potential customers.</description></item><item><title>Marketing crash course</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/marketing-crash-course/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/marketing-crash-course/</guid><description>Tags: #permanent-notes Relevant Notes Notes Marketing is about communicating value to your customers and connecting with them–why should they care? How we create vallue to these customers? Pillars of marketing Product Price Place Promotion Basics Customer research This involves learning about your customer. Explore the following: 1.) Demographics, 2.) Geographic, and 3.) Psychologic. Competitive research Learn about the different competitors in the same field.</description></item><item><title>Marketing getting hired</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/marketing-getting-hired/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/marketing-getting-hired/</guid><description>Tags: Relevant Notes marketing Notes Find something that makes you stand out. People want people who are creative.1 Give a unique input in ways that people can grow their business. Don&amp;rsquo;t just give something generic like spending more on ads, etc. Ex. Break down why their copy is terrible, show stats of other sites, creative platforms that they are not leveraging yet Show that you ==want to get above and beyond.</description></item><item><title>Marketing MOC</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/marketing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/marketing/</guid><description>MOCs Branding MOC Digital marketing MOC Overarching Marketing crash course Pillars of marketing Branches of marketing Strategies &amp;amp; campaigns Marketing tooling Strategic marketing plan Marketing analytics Launch marketing Marketing campaigns Writing for marketers People Behavioral segmentation Marketing research Customer Relationship Management Monitoring Marketing growth Tips/ rules/ insights What works for social does not work for organic Getting hired marketing-getting-hired Dump Podcast notes dump Case study notes Learn at the top of my head Referal programs Sources/ Stacks Free templates for marketing</description></item><item><title>Marketing podcast notes dump</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/marketing-podcast-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/marketing-podcast-notes/</guid><description> #2: Neil &amp;amp; Eric&amp;rsquo;s Biggest Marketing Wins - Marketing School - Digital Marketing and Online Marketing Tips | Podcast on Spotify Sign-up vs log-in Email updates Content update: &amp;ldquo;10 MORE&amp;rdquo; vs &amp;ldquo;10&amp;rdquo; only Detailed guides–be more details so you reach more keywords, link to guides from everywhere on your site</description></item><item><title>Marketing Research</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/marketing-research/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/marketing-research/</guid><description> Buyer personas</description></item><item><title>marketing-growth</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/marketing-growth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/marketing-growth/</guid><description> Tags: #come-back Relevant Notes Sources Growth reporting Growth Reporting - Google Sheets Notes Highlights</description></item><item><title>marketing-tooling</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/marketing-tooling/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/marketing-tooling/</guid><description> Tags: #repository Relevant Notes Tools Google Analytics Google Search Console ADREFS [] Sources #3: Neil &amp;amp; Eric&amp;rsquo;s Favorite Marketing Tools - Marketing School - Digital Marketing and Online Marketing Tips | Podcast on Spotify</description></item><item><title>Mental Health MOC</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/mental-health/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/mental-health/</guid><description> Mental health is political Never be afraid to ask for help Self-awareness Personality tests Burnout Mindfulness</description></item><item><title>Mental Models MOC</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/mental-models/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/mental-models/</guid><description>#in-progress/garden
Occam&amp;rsquo;s razor OODA loop Levels of magnification Refraction thinking Lindy effect Refraction thinking Hanlon&amp;rsquo;s razor</description></item><item><title>Navigating the Garden</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/home/navigate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/home/navigate/</guid><description>Hello! 👋 Thank you so much for being here! In this page, I map out how this garden is structured for ease of navigation. There are a lot of links &amp;amp; backlinks, so it can get confusing! 😵‍💫
Structure 🏛 Digital gardens are composed of notes that are interlinked for the purpose of linking thinking. As such, there are notes inside notes.
I structured my garden in this manner from when you navigate from the homepage.</description></item><item><title>Never be afraid to ask for help</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/help/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/help/</guid><description>Tags: #permanent-notes Relevant Notes life-advice vulnerability Notes There&amp;rsquo;s nothing wrong with asking for help. The idea of how some people appear successful/ &amp;ldquo;perfect&amp;rdquo; may create a barrier for them to becoming vulnerable. This prevents them from asking for help and lets them suffer along in private pain. You cannot help others till you learn how to ask yourself. Highlights 7 Cups for the Searching Soul | The 7 Cups Community &amp;ldquo;If you are ashamed of admitting that you have problems, then you cannot ask for help.</description></item><item><title>obsidian</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/obsidian/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/obsidian/</guid><description>Helpful Links 100 OBSIDIAN TIPS: Beginner to Advanced in 24 Minutes | Obsidian Tutorial - YouTube Queries in Obsidian Markdown Cheat Sheet | Markdown Guide [Mobile] Setting up iOS git-based syncing with mobile app (using Working Copy) - Share &amp;amp; showcase - Obsidian Forum Will set-up GitHub - blacksmithgu/obsidian-dataview: A complex query language implementation for the Obsidian note-taking tool.</description></item><item><title>On choosing your commitments</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/choosing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/choosing/</guid><description> Tags: #personal-learnings Relevant Notes Notes It&amp;rsquo;s better to undercommit than overcommit Choose to maximize your impact Strive for quantity &amp;gt; quality Employers look at value of experience, growth, and impact, NOT how many interships you had Highlights</description></item><item><title>On Digital Gardens</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/home/garden/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/home/garden/</guid><description>This digital garden is one of my personal projects this year! I&amp;rsquo;m still learning if there&amp;rsquo;s a proper way of setting it up.
I realized how unconducive for permanence my past notes were. I literally have too much bookmark managers + mind dumps (thanks Apple Notes, Telegram, Messenger, Mem.ai for keeping up with me).
This digital garden serves as my personal knowledge management system. I&amp;rsquo;m a really forgetful person who tends to highlight stuff and tbh rarely comes back to them!</description></item><item><title>On expressing emotions</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/expressing-emotions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/expressing-emotions/</guid><description> We often think someone doesn&amp;rsquo;t express emotion because they don&amp;rsquo;t want to, but what if they just don&amp;rsquo;t feel any</description></item><item><title>On Relating to Others</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/relating-to-others/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/relating-to-others/</guid><description> Tags: #permanent-notes Relevant Notes learning-thinking-communicating Notes Relating others requires conscious effort and conscious choices. You do not get better at it immediately. Highlights Relating to others is also a process we learn consciously that eventually becomes unconscious.1 7 Cups for the Searching Soul &amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;</description></item><item><title>Personal Knowledge Management</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/pkm-tools/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/pkm-tools/</guid><description> Tags: #repository Relevant Notes Tools Obsidian Notion Mem.ai</description></item><item><title>Personal Knowledge Management</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/pkm/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/pkm/</guid><description> Zettelkasten Learning in public</description></item><item><title>Personality Tests</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/personality-tests/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/personality-tests/</guid><description>Tags: #repository #in-progress/garden Relevant Notes Self-awareness Tests My results are here lol. 👻
Enneagram I like the enneagram test because there are a looot of resources about working with enneagram styles as well as the performance of each personality depending on their health level. This is also the test that made me fall in love with personality tests lol.</description></item><item><title>Pillars of marketing</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/pillars-of-marketing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/pillars-of-marketing/</guid><description>Tags: Relevant Notes Notes From: 4 Ps of Marketing - Templates | Tettra Context: Share information here about why you’re doing this exercise as a team. If you have multiple product lines and/or services, clarify which one you plan to focus on. Stakeholders: Take note here of who is involved in this conversation and which perspectives are being represented. The four Ps are: Product What product or service do we sell?</description></item><item><title>Politics</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/politics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/politics/</guid><description> Health is political Mental health is political Design is political x Decolonizing design Art is political</description></item><item><title>Positive Leadership</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/positive-leadership/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/positive-leadership/</guid><description> Tags: #in-progress/garden</description></item><item><title>Press Release</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/press-release/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/press-release/</guid><description>Tags: #permanent-notes Relevant Notes writing References Using Press Releases in Your Marketing Strategy | MARION How to Write a Great Partnership Press Release | AllBusiness.com 10 examples of effective press releases + a template to download General Highlights What should be in a press release?1 the main announcement relevant dates locations contact information Notes on writing1 Make it short, digestible, and skimmable.</description></item><item><title>Productivity MOC</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/productivity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/productivity/</guid><description>Tags: #in-progress/garden #come-back
MOCs Productivity systems MOC PKM MOC Concepts Choosing priorities Flow state Deep focus Attentional spaces Techniques Time blocking Unlocking Don&amp;rsquo;t fall into the overconfidence bias trap Avoid multitasking Deconstructing constructs &amp;ldquo;Screw motivation, what you need is discipline&amp;rdquo; Laziness does not exist Keep in mind Perfection is the enemy of progress</description></item><item><title>Productivity Systems MOC</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/productivity-systems-moc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/productivity-systems-moc/</guid><description>Tags: #in-progress/garden Relevant Notes Systems To-do List Must-do List Must-Should-Want Getting Things Done Zen To Done Pomodoro Technique Time-blocking The Eisenhower Matrix The Moscow Method The Kanban Method Don’t Break the Chain The Daily Trifecta Bullet journalling Seinfeld Calendar System Eat that frog The SMART method MoSCoW method Sources Is there a perfect productivity system?</description></item><item><title>Project Management MOC</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/proj-man/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/proj-man/</guid><description> Roadmapping Agile methodology</description></item><item><title>Psychological Safety</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/psychological-safety/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/psychological-safety/</guid><description>Tags: #permanent-notes Relevant Notes leadership Notes While there is an idea that creating time for check-ins/ socio-emotional involvement within the team, it&amp;rsquo;s always an investment. Good working environments/ good working cultures foster creativity and good dynamics within the team. Highlights &amp;ldquo;The behaviors that create psychological safety — conversational turn-taking and empathy — are part of the same unwritten rules we often turn to, as individuals, when we need to establish a bond.</description></item><item><title>Psychology MOC</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/psychology/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/psychology/</guid><description> Therapy Biases Confirmation Bias Availability Bias Collective effervesence–We thrive more when we&amp;rsquo;re with others Emotions are contagious We weren&amp;rsquo;t build to be alone When we have a problem, we tend to go with solutions that involve adding something than taking something existing away On expressing emotions Languishing Yerkes-Dodson Law Burnout Stress</description></item><item><title>Public speaking</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/public-speaking/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/public-speaking/</guid><description>Tags: #permanent-notes Relevant Notes leadership Notes Speak slower and pause more. Create dramatic effect to your speech. Don&amp;rsquo;t eat up your words. Avoid making it scripted and rigid. It&amp;rsquo;s not about formality. Focus on connection. Highlights How to Become a Better Public Speaker When you&amp;rsquo;re public speaking try to speak slower and pause more. Being able to use pauses and own your stage can make your speech a lot more powerful and confident.</description></item><item><title>Quotes on Stoicism</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/stoic-quotes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/stoic-quotes/</guid><description>Source: Tags: #philosophy Relevant Notes Thoughts: Quotes “We are often more frightened than hurt; and we suffer more from imagination than from reality.” — Seneca “It’s silly to try to escape other people’s faults. They are inescapable. Just try to escape your own.” —Marcus Aurelius “Our life is what our thoughts make it.” — Marcus Aurelius “If anyone tells you that a certain person speaks ill— of you, do not make excuses about what is said of you but answer, ‘He was ignorant of my other faults, else he would not have mentioned these alone.</description></item><item><title>research</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/research/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/research/</guid><description> Surveys Distilled research ecosystem</description></item><item><title>Research Plan</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/research-plan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/research-plan/</guid><description>Tags: #permanent-notes Relevant Notes User research Notes Basic plan1
Research objectives Research questions Survey questions and types Survey participants Highlights How to Create and Run an Effective Survey | Maze 1 Research objectives What you’re doing, why you’re doing it, and what you hope to learn Research questions Questions that you’re hoping the research will answer (not what you want surveyees to answer) Survey questions and types Questions you will ask in the survey to help uncover insights about the research questions Survey participants Who are the people you want to survey and why?</description></item><item><title>Roadmap</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/home/roadmap/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/home/roadmap/</guid><description>I have super scrappy baseline knowledge in code. I only reached up to midway of my FreeCodeCamp journey so I&amp;rsquo;m.. lost&amp;hellip;. and reliant on Google search lol. I&amp;rsquo;m documenting my journey here at Building this website. Currently&amp;hellip; Fixing the broken links Fixing the notes tagged #in-progress/garden (also will I ever lol) Concretizing my system 🍃 Revisiting my old notes in Notion, Notes, Mem, Telegram, Messenger, Discord, etc. I really wish I learned about Obsidian earlier grr.</description></item><item><title>Roadmapping</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/project-roadmapping/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/project-roadmapping/</guid><description>Tags: #in-progress/garden Relevant Notes Date: [[08-08-2021]]
What I want this note to contain What is roadmapping Why roadmaps Facilitating roadmapping sessions (check: facilitation ) Current ideas Miro/ Figma collaboration board Align with vision and create KPIs Where do we want to see project for next months with sticky notes Voting process Finalization of roadmap &amp;amp; presentation Notes How to facilitate a roadmapping session Method 1 Prior Assign a decider &amp;amp; facilitator During Set goals (vision/ mission).</description></item><item><title>Search Engine Optimization</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/seo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/seo/</guid><description> SEO writing</description></item><item><title>Self-awareness</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/self-awareness/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/self-awareness/</guid><description>#in-progress/garden</description></item><item><title>SEO Writing</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/seo-writing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/seo-writing/</guid><description>Tags: #in-progress/garden Relevant Notes Notes Highlights How SEO Writing assistant works (from SEMrush newsletter_ Specify the ==keywords you’d like your article to rank for.== Start typing a new piece or copy-paste an existing article. Find out how well your article is optimized already and get immediate recommendations that will help your article rank higher: ==What other phrases to include== (hello, related keywords!) How to improve readability (tone of voice, sentence structure, text length, etc.</description></item><item><title>Shape Up</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/shape-up/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/shape-up/</guid><description> Tags: #read-queue #come-back Relevant Notes Resource https://basecamp.com/shapeup/shape-up.pdf</description></item><item><title>Should you send a thank you note?</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/ty-note/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/ty-note/</guid><description>Tags: #pondering #permanent-notes Relevant Notes career-advice Notes TLDR; Yes. Highlights Thanks or no thanks? Sending a note1
They suggest: Sending a note. Making it handwritten or digital. Making it personal. Showing that you’re interested in the job. Showing that you paid attention to the conversation. Eno Eka I always send a thank you note/ email and I advise my clients to do so because: It is the polite thing to do.</description></item><item><title>Social Change MOC</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/social-change/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/social-change/</guid><description> in-progress Feminism MOC Activism MOC</description></item><item><title>Sources</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/sources/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/sources/</guid><description> Design Tools &amp;amp; Sources UX design sources Websites Books</description></item><item><title>Sources on Stoicism</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/sources-stoicism/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/sources-stoicism/</guid><description> Tags: #repository #in-progress/garden #come-back Relevant Notes Sources Books The Daily Stoic Podcasts The Daily Stoic Courses Skillshare Stoicism Masterclass</description></item><item><title>Stoicism MOC</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/stoicism/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/stoicism/</guid><description>I regularly update my Are.na on Stoicism. The good life is anywhere–you don&amp;rsquo;t have to wait for a certain destination Avoid being reactive Let go of things that are outside of your control Do not let other people take up your mental space Unsorted Stoic Values How to be Stoic Quotes on Stoicism Sources</description></item><item><title>strategic-marketing-plan</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/strategic-marketing-plan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/strategic-marketing-plan/</guid><description> Tags: #permanent-notes Relevant Notes References Strategic Marketing Plan - Template - Google Docs Adam Erhart August 19, 2021 Newsletter: The Modern Marketing Masterplan Notes Marketing plan core
Model - What you sell and how you deliver it Market - The right people to sell to Message - the right things to say Media - the right place to reach the right people Machine - The right system and series to make it all happen automatically Sample Strategic Marketing Plan - Template - Google Docs Purpose One-line purpose of your company or product Core Values One or two sentences (or a bullet list of three to five things) that describe how the values that define your work as a marketing team Target Demographic One-line description of the market you are trying to reach Brand Promise One-line brand promise (think of your product’s tagline) Elevator Pitch Three-line elevator pitch 3-Year Target One-line, three-year goal Annual goals Year Start value Current value Target value Goal 1 Goal 2 Goal 3 Quarterly/monthly/cycle goals Year Start value Current value Target value Goal 1 Goal 2 Goal 3 Priority projects Project 1 (% complete) Project 2 (% complete) Project 3 (% complete) Highlights</description></item><item><title>Surveys</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/surveys/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/surveys/</guid><description>Tags: #permanent-notes Relevant Notes Focus on the user and all else will follow Human-centric design UX design Notes Start with a Research plan Survey design Be inclusive (pronouns!) Make it short &amp;amp; concise Make it consistent Avoid prediction &amp;amp; recall questions Highlights User research Survey Design Guide: Process, Principles, and Questions | Maze 1 When to use surveys To get a sense of user sentiment for an existing product or shortly after launch To gauge interest in a future concept or idea and determine what new products or features should be prioritized To gather demographic information about your users and their needs To dig deeper into a known problem are Scenarios to use During an unmoderated test to gather further feedback to complement your customers’ behavior Follow-up Standalone initiative to gather feedback Creating Create Research plan Align with your team Create the survey Test the survey Launch 🚀 Monitor Survey design principles to keep in mind Align with your stakeholders Set the right expectations with your team Don&amp;rsquo;t miss the pilot test Be intentional Make it valuable Keep it consistent Avoid asking for sensitive information whenever possible Ensure inclusivity Keep things concise Keep it engaging Avoid leading questions and priming Create space for your customers' voice Keep respondents informed Account for order effects Negativity is stronger Prediction and recall are not reliable Avoid asking questions that ask your participant to recall something late in the past or predict their future behavior.</description></item><item><title>Systems thinking</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/systems-thinking/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/systems-thinking/</guid><description> Tags: #to-digest Relevant Notes mental-models productivity-systems-moc Notes Highlights “In the most basic sense, a system is any group of interacting, interrelated, or interdependent parts that form a complex and unified whole that has a specific purpose.” Ironically, our brain hates thinking since it needs energy that can be utilized elsewhere. By creating systems, we make this process easier and faster.</description></item><item><title>Technology MOC"</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/technology/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/technology/</guid><description> Cybersecurity MOC</description></item><item><title>The good life is anywhere–you don't have to wait for a certain destination</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/good-life-is-anywhere/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/good-life-is-anywhere/</guid><description>Tags: #permanent-notes
Relevant Notes
We often think that happiness should come when we receive xyz or finally get abc, but we shouldn&amp;rsquo;t think of happiness/ a good life as something conditional that happens when we reach a certain point. Instead, we can claim it now.
For reflection “At this moment you aren’t on a journey, but wandering about, being driven from place to place, even though what you seek—to live well—is found in all places.</description></item><item><title>Therapy</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/therapy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/therapy/</guid><description> Cognitive behavioral therapy</description></item><item><title>To Read</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/to-read/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/to-read/</guid><description>Tags: #come-back
Reading (probably long lol) How can we develop transformative tools for thought? Design of Everyday Things Haven&amp;rsquo;t read How to grow liveable worlds: Ten (not-so-easy) steps for life in the Planthroposcene How to Professionally Deal With Your Bad Boss hr Why You Click with Certain People psychology To revisit &amp;amp; take notes 07/31: Read these before and posted these somewhere, want to read them again since I didn&amp;rsquo;t take notes!</description></item><item><title>Tooling</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/tooling/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/tooling/</guid><description> Note: in-progress lol empty
Personal Knowledge Management Tools Design Tools &amp;amp; Sources General curations Fardeen&amp;rsquo;s Curated tools Uneed. The best tools of the internet.</description></item><item><title>UX Design</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/ux-design/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/ux-design/</guid><description> Related to: Design MOC Art of questioning in UX design Focus on the user and all else will follow Critiquing a design Case studies in UX design UX Tools</description></item><item><title>UX design sources</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/ux-design-sources/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/ux-design-sources/</guid><description>UX Research Guide to UXR</description></item><item><title>Visual Design</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/visual/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/visual/</guid><description> Tags: #in-progress/garden Relevant Notes Sources A Basic Visual Design Framework #read-queue</description></item><item><title>Vulnerability</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/vulnerability/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/vulnerability/</guid><description>Tags: Relevant Notes Notes Practice vulnerability in your approach. Stay authentic. Highlights Concepts We become closer with people when we’re vulnerable.12 It’s easy for us to think that we’re too selfish, but in fact, most of us aren’t anywhere near selfish enough. We’re not used to putting our own needs, wants, desires centre stage because we’re ‘good’ people.12 Cases Instead of asking “what do you do?</description></item><item><title>We should learn to embrace mediocrity</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/projects/embrace-mediocrity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/projects/embrace-mediocrity/</guid><description>Date: 08052021
Tags: #in-progress/garden #projects Relevant Notes 202108031836 Grounding Why? To break the construct that we should work our ass off in order to achieve societal acceptance To break the social construct that settling is incorrect To impart the concept the it&amp;rsquo;s okay to be mediocre To advocate for prioritizing health over outward sense-seeking How? Share about current societal standards and how it does more harm than good Expose problem of hustle culture Current rates of mental health conditions in PH, especially in working age (if the statistics of this exists!</description></item><item><title>We weren't build to be alone</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/not-alone/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/not-alone/</guid><description> Tags: #to-digest Relevant Notes collective-effervesence Notes Highlights Psychologists find that in cultures where people pursue happiness individually, they may actually become lonelier. But in cultures where they pursue happiness socially — through connecting, caring and contributing — people appear to be more likely to gain well-being.1 There’s a Specific Kind of Joy We’ve Been Missing &amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;</description></item><item><title>Websites</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/websites/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/websites/</guid><description> Ethics Litmus Tests</description></item><item><title>What do recruiters want?</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/what-do-recruiters-want/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/what-do-recruiters-want/</guid><description> Tags: #in-progress/garden Relevant Notes Notes Highlights 20 Situational Interview Questions and Answers to Nail Your Interview 1 Dependable Positive attitude Self-starters Team players Good organization Work well under pressure Communication skill 20 Situational Interview Questions and Answers to Nail Your Interview &amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;</description></item><item><title>What to answer to 'mamamatay rin tayong lahat'</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/mamamatay/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/mamamatay/</guid><description>Tags: #personal-learnings Relevant Notes This may seem.. morbid. While I do admit that I sometimes say &amp;ldquo;Mamamatay din tayong lahat&amp;rdquo; in an escapist manner (albeit true), I do acknowledge that it is true, comforting, and a good way to move forward when it comes to handling problems. However, this acceptance into the finite nature of life also makes one prone to not living ceasing each day.
Embracing stoicism is a good way to avoid that mistake.</description></item><item><title>What to Learn</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/what-to-learn/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/what-to-learn/</guid><description> Tags: #repository Relevant Notes Learning Where to Learn Sources What skills do you recommend I pick up via online courses? - DearTBC</description></item><item><title>What works for social does not work for organic</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/facebook-v-organic/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/facebook-v-organic/</guid><description> Tags: #permanent-notes Relevant Notes marketing-tooling Notes What works for social does not work for organic. It&amp;rsquo;s important to search for the keywords that are good for both/ either.[^1] References #3: Neil &amp;amp; Eric&amp;rsquo;s Favorite Marketing Tools - Marketing School - Digital Marketing and Online Marketing Tips | Podcast on Spotify</description></item><item><title>When to quit a job?</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/quit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/quit/</guid><description>Tags: #to-digest Relevant Notes work-culture life-sentence Notes Highlights 15 Warning Signs Your Job Isn&amp;rsquo;t The Right Fit For You1 Job doesn&amp;rsquo;t let you use your strengths Work with manager to explore how to incorporate more of these opportunities in your role Feeling overly negative about work Constantly overwhelmed Lost passion Can&amp;rsquo;t answer &amp;ldquo;what gets you out of bed in the morning?</description></item><item><title>When we have a problem, we tend to go with solutions that involve adding something than taking something existing away</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/adding-than-taking/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/adding-than-taking/</guid><description>Tags: #permanent-notes Relevant Notes hanlon Notes Highlights When faced with a problem, people tend to select solutions that involve adding new elements rather than taking existing components away.1 The researchers first carried out a set of observational studies, assessments without a control group, to see whether this bias existed at all. In one, they asked 91 participants to make a pattern symmetrical by either adding or removing colored boxes.</description></item><item><title>Where to Learn</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/where-to-learn/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/where-to-learn/</guid><description> Tags: #in-progress/garden #repository Relevant Notes Learning What to Learn General Courses Skillshare Coursera LinkedIn Learning Udemy FutureLearn Self-school Design x Tech Events General Assembly The Gynasium Courses FreeCodeCamp Hyperlink Gymnasium Business GoTo Stage Languages Memrise</description></item><item><title>Work Culture</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/work-culture/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/work-culture/</guid><description>Tags: #permanent-notes Relevant Notes leadership positive-leadership psychological-safety Concepts Burnout is an organizational issue Notes Good vs bad work culture Good work culture involves psychological-safety Tools for enhancing connection between team Figma Design Team Trading Cards Highlights Good vs bad work culture Bad work culture Signs company is badly managed1 Employees are fleeing.</description></item><item><title>Work ethics</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/work-ethics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/work-ethics/</guid><description> Good work ethics in remote work</description></item><item><title>Work Structures</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/work-structures/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/work-structures/</guid><description> Shape Up</description></item><item><title>Workplace communication</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/workplace-comm/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/workplace-comm/</guid><description> How to apologize</description></item><item><title>Workplace equity</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/workplace-equity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/workplace-equity/</guid><description>Tags: #permanent-notes #pondering Relevant Notes leadership Notes Distribute tasks between men and women There is a societal expectation for women to volunteer more in non-promotable tasks. This culture holds back women. &amp;ldquo;Not only is their advancement stymied, but also corporations miss out on capturing valuable talent.&amp;quot;1 Managers should take conscious effort into distributing work with equity. Highlights Why Women Volunteer for Tasks That Don’t Lead to Promotions 1 Our studies demonstrate that although neither men nor women really want to volunteer for thankless tasks, women volunteer more, are asked to volunteer more, and accept requests to volunteer more than men.</description></item><item><title>Writing for marketers</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/writing-for-marketers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/writing-for-marketers/</guid><description> Tags: Relevant Notes writing Sources Power Words | Fomo - Google Sheets Notes Highlights</description></item><item><title>Writing MOC</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/writing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/writing/</guid><description> How to be a better writer</description></item><item><title>Writing projects</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/writing-projects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/moc/writing-projects/</guid><description>Fin Interplays of Mathematics and Classism – Math 10 2021 Capstone #in-progress 08052021 We should learn to embrace mediocrity 08072021 How I give feedback School stuff lol #writing-prompt #ideas On redefining beauty When should we trade off excellence for sanity? [There are things I want to keep buried]</description></item><item><title>Yerkes-Dodson-law</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/yerkes-dodson-law/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/yerkes-dodson-law/</guid><description>Tags: Relevant Notes Burnout References Yerkes - Dodson Law - Psychestudy Episode 3: Burnout in Online Classes - Psych Speaks: A Mental Health Podcast Series | Podcast on Spotify Notes Stress is something that we need at optimal amounts. It helps us keep going and improve. However, it is best to keep this at an optimal level wherein you are not compromising yourself.</description></item><item><title>Your career is not a life sentence</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/life-sentence/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/life-sentence/</guid><description>Tags: #permanent-notes Relevant Notes stoicism Notes Highlights &amp;ldquo;We must not get so wrapped up in our work that we think we’re immune from the reality of aging and life. Who wants to be the person who can never let go? Is there so little meaning in your life that your only pursuit is work until you’re eventually carted off in a coffin? Take pride in your work.</description></item><item><title>Zettelkasten</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/zettelkasten/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/zettelkasten/</guid><description> Tags: #come-back Relevant Notes Notes Don&amp;rsquo;t fall into the collector&amp;rsquo;s fallacy Highlights</description></item></channel></rss>