<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Notes on</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/</link><description>Recent content in Notes on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About Me</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/home/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/home/about/</guid><description>👋 Hello! I&amp;rsquo;m Chloe Abrasada. I actually have a second name that I don&amp;rsquo;t use for branding purposes (jkjk). I&amp;rsquo;m a productivity nerd 👩‍🏫, web lurker 💻, and design enthusiast 🎨.
📚 I&amp;rsquo;m an incoming third year student in UP Manila studying Occupational Therapy. Outside school, I part time as a designer and volunteer in NGOs related to my cause. 🍃
🔗 Links I publish my works here at my portfolio and Behance .</description></item><item><title>Active Listening</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/perdev/kindness/active-listening/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/perdev/kindness/active-listening/</guid><description>Tags: #permanent-notes Relevant Notes mental-health Notes Active listening involves consciously paying attention to who you&amp;rsquo;re listening to. Skills Reflection Labelling emotions Asking questions Empathy Lived experienced Identify strengths It involves mindfulness. Self-awareness is important. Be aware of Listening filters Personal thoughts Show you&amp;rsquo;re listening through body language/ PEA approach Highlights Active listening is a great technique to help people feel better when they are going through hard times, dealing with loss, struggling with health issues, or just need to vent.</description></item><item><title>Art of questioning in UX design</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/arts-tech/ux-design/art-of-questioning/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/arts-tech/ux-design/art-of-questioning/</guid><description>Tags: #to-digest Relevant Notes learning-thinking-communicating ethics-in-tech #come-back Notes Highlights 59 Questions for Mindful UX Design — This Too Shall Grow 1 Exploratory questions ==What would you dislike about being a user of this product?== What’s the worst scenario that could happen because of this product? Are you OK with your loved ones knowing you worked on this? Are you OK with the users knowing you worked on this?</description></item><item><title>Availability bias</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/sciences/psycho/availability-bias/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/sciences/psycho/availability-bias/</guid><description>Tags: #permanent-notes Relevant Notes Notes Believing what&amp;rsquo;s convenient Believing what we connect most to ourself Highlights Availability bias is the tendency to rely on information that’s readily available, instead of what’s actually more relevant to the situation. In the context of workplace relationships, this often leads us to connect other people’s behavior to ourselves, because those are the experiences that are already occupying our mental space.</description></item><item><title>Avoid being reactive</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/philosophy/stoicism/avoid-being-reactive/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/philosophy/stoicism/avoid-being-reactive/</guid><description> Tags: #permanent-notes
Relevant Notes
Let go of things that are outside of your control For reflection “You must stop blaming God, and not blame any person. You must completely control your desire and shift your avoidance to what lies within your reasoned choice. You must no longer feel anger, resentment, envy, or regret.”—EPICTETUS, DISCOURSES, 3.22.1</description></item><item><title>Biases</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/sciences/psycho/biases/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/sciences/psycho/biases/</guid><description> Confirmation bias Availability bias</description></item><item><title>Books</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/sources/books/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/sources/books/</guid><description> Ikigai by Francesc Miralles and Hector Garcia Atomic Habits by James Clear</description></item><item><title>Building this Website</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/home/building-this-website/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/home/building-this-website/</guid><description>Oldest to latest 07/26/2021 Quartz Set-up 07/27/2021 Site actually FINALLY up lol struggled through that What I didn&amp;rsquo;t know before this lol Wikilinks don&amp;rsquo;t work on Github Pages Doesn&amp;rsquo;t support spaces 07/29/2021 Fixed backlinks What I didn&amp;rsquo;t know before this There was an error in my config.toml 07/29/2021 Change color of page 07/31/2021 Add &amp;ldquo;Let&amp;rsquo;s go back&amp;rdquo; on 404 How to make an HTML back link 08/01/2021 Add date late updated at footer Last modified date of a file on a website 08/01/2021 Add changelog at footer Obsidian Vault changelog plug-in What I didn&amp;rsquo;t know before this Won&amp;rsquo;t really work without frontmatter 08/02/2021 Add option to remove TOC 08/03/2021 Add arrow to external links Superscript in CSS only?</description></item><item><title>Changelog</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/changelog/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/changelog/</guid><description> 2021-08-05 at 22h17 · [[about]] 2021-08-05 at 22h17 · [[books]] 2021-08-05 at 22h15 · [[pondering]] 2021-08-05 at 22h12 · [[tooling]] 2021-08-05 at 22h12 · [[social-change]] 2021-08-05 at 22h02 · [[ethics-activities]] 2021-08-05 at 22h02 · [[ethics]] 2021-08-05 at 22h00 · [[_index]] 2021-08-05 at 21h59 · [[websites]] 2021-08-05 at 21h59 · [[sources]] 2021-08-05 at 20h17 · [[embrace-mediocrity]] 2021-08-05 at 20h17 · [[writing-projects]] 2021-08-05 at 20h16 · [[design]] 2021-08-05 at 20h12 · [[navigate]] 2021-08-05 at 20h09 · [[art-of-questioning]] 2021-08-05 at 20h05 · [[hanlon]] 2021-08-05 at 20h05 · [[to-read]] 2021-08-05 at 20h05 · [[politics]] 2021-08-05 at 20h05 · [[ux-design]] 2021-08-05 at 20h05 · [[surveys]]</description></item><item><title>Check your privilege</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/perdev/life-advice/privilege/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/perdev/life-advice/privilege/</guid><description>Tags: Relevant Notes life-advice relating Notes Quotes “Some people are sharp and others dull; some are raised in a better environment, others in worse, the latter, having inferior habits and nurture, will require more by way of proof and careful instruction to master these teachings and to be formed by them—in the same way that bodies in a bad state must be given a great deal of care when perfect health is sought.</description></item><item><title>Chloe's Corner</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/home/corner/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/home/corner/</guid><description> Note: #in-progress/garden
Tooling To Read</description></item><item><title>Circular Economy</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/environmental-educ/circular-economy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/environmental-educ/circular-economy/</guid><description>Tags: #in-progress/garden #to-digest Relevant Notes Notes Highlights How Circular is the Circular Economy? - Local Futures 1
In the circular economy, resources would be continually re-used, meaning that there would be no more mining activity or waste production. The stress is on recycling, made possible by designing products so that they can easily be taken apart.
Several scientific studies (see references) describe the concept as an “idealised vision”, a “mix of various ideas from different domains”, or a “vague idea based on pseudo-scientific concepts”.</description></item><item><title>Collective Effervesence</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/sciences/psycho/collective-effervesence/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/sciences/psycho/collective-effervesence/</guid><description>Tags: #permanent-notes Relevant Notes notes/sciences/psycho/emotions-contagious Notes Highlights We find our greatest bliss in moments of collective effervescence. It’s a concept coined in the early 20th century by the pioneering sociologist Émile Durkheim to describe the sense of energy and harmony people feel when they come together in a group around a shared purpose. Collective effervescence is the synchrony you feel when you slide into rhythm with strangers on a dance floor, colleagues in a brainstorming session, cousins at a religious service or teammates on a soccer field.</description></item><item><title>collector-fallacy</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/productivity/collector-fallacy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/productivity/collector-fallacy/</guid><description>Tags: #permanent-notes Relevant Notes Notes Fallacy: As you collect, your knowledge grows But what actually happens is that you don&amp;rsquo;t process and digest these notes Although a lengthy process, take time to convert these notes into ones you actually learn, know, and digest&amp;ndash;you don&amp;rsquo;t learn just by highlighting Highlights The Collector’s Fallacy • Zettelkasten Method The worst we could do is to pile up copies until the stack grows intimidatingly high, until it becomes unmanageable.</description></item><item><title>Confirmation Bias</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/sciences/psycho/confirmation-bias/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/sciences/psycho/confirmation-bias/</guid><description>Tags: #in-progress/garden #to-digest Relevant Notes Notes Highlights On the other hand, confirmation bias is at play when you seek out information that fits in with how you already see the world. Confirmation bias can seriously harm your relationships, especially if you have any negative associations with your employer, workplace, or anyone on your team.1 How Teams Can Be More Supportive With Help From Hanlon’s Razor &amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;</description></item><item><title>critiquing-design</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/arts-tech/ux-design/critiquing-design/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/arts-tech/ux-design/critiquing-design/</guid><description>Tags: #to-digest Relevant Notes Notes Highlights Julie Zhuo on Twitter: &amp;ldquo;Everyone has an opinion on design. There&amp;rsquo;s always an immediate gut reaction: &amp;ldquo;Ooh, I love this!&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Meh.&amp;rdquo; But how do you go beyond that to honing your skills of giving helpful, actionable feedback? Here are the 7 questions I run through when critiquing a product&amp;rsquo;s design 👇&amp;rdquo; / Twitter What is the user journey to get here?</description></item><item><title>Design is political x Decolonizing design</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/arts-tech/design/decolonizing-design/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/arts-tech/design/decolonizing-design/</guid><description>Tags: #permanent-notes Relevant Notes Notes Western ideologies have shaped our concepts of &amp;ldquo;preferable design&amp;rdquo; Anything outside these Western preferences are seen as different We should remove the distinction of art and craft1 The concept of a difference between art and craft reflect classist distinctions from the West Highlights What Does It Mean to Decolonize Design? 2
“Colonization” is rooted in indigenous peoples’ experiences of oppression—specifically, the seizure of native resources, as well as the embedding of Western ideology into society The work designers make is inspired by taste, and taste is often derived from what we’re exposed to during our upbringing.</description></item><item><title>Design Teams</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/arts-tech/design/design-teams/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/arts-tech/design/design-teams/</guid><description>Tags: #permanent-notes Relevant Notes leadership in design work-culture Notes How to build a design team Work cultures &amp;amp; environments are different–we hire people that would complement the team. The filtering process is important as every member contributes to the overall flow of the team Baseline process: How well will this person work with the team culture? What are our values?</description></item><item><title>Design-tools</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/arts-tech/design/design-tools/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/arts-tech/design/design-tools/</guid><description> Tags: #repository Online Design Tools Photopea Staying Inspired Muzli 2 - Stay Inspired</description></item><item><title>Don't be afraid of failure</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/perdev/life-advice/afraid-failure/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/perdev/life-advice/afraid-failure/</guid><description> Tags: #extra-push #permanent-notes Relevant Notes career-advice feedback Notes Your good ideas are hidden under the bad ones Your first 50 attempts will be terrible, so go ahead and use them up Highlights</description></item><item><title>Emotions are contagious</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/sciences/psycho/emotions-contagious/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/sciences/psycho/emotions-contagious/</guid><description>Tags: #permanent-notes Relevant Notes collective-effervesence Notes You feel the emotions around the people around you. Collective anxiety, Zoom fatigue, etc. Highlights When the pandemic began in 2020, the first negative emotion to spread was fear. Waves of panic crashed through communities, compelling people to purify packages and hoard hand sanitizer. As too many people lost loved ones, too many others lost jobs and everyone lost some semblance of normal life.</description></item><item><title>Empathy</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/perdev/kindness/empathy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/perdev/kindness/empathy/</guid><description> We are unkind because we our empathy is limited Empathy is in admitting that we don&amp;rsquo;t understand</description></item><item><title>Ethics Activities</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/philosophy/ethics/ethics-activities/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/philosophy/ethics/ethics-activities/</guid><description> Ethics Litmus Tests PDF Version</description></item><item><title>Faux Activism</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/soc-sci/activism/faux-activism/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/soc-sci/activism/faux-activism/</guid><description>#in-progress/garden
Sources How social justice slideshows made by activists took over Instagram - Vox to-read</description></item><item><title>Feedback</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/perdev/leadership/feedback/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/perdev/leadership/feedback/</guid><description>Tags: #might-publish #personal-learnings Related to: No to micromanaging life-advice I really value the importance of giving feedback. Our words are too powerful to impart things callously. I&amp;rsquo;ve seen people give feedback differently, and I think there&amp;rsquo;s no super perfect formula into giving it because people are so unpredictable and subjective. I adjust my approach, but what I always seek to maintain is to relay feedback in a constructive manner that helps a person move forward concretely.</description></item><item><title>Focus on your user and everything else will follow</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/arts-tech/ux-design/focus-on-user/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/arts-tech/ux-design/focus-on-user/</guid><description> Tags: #to-digest Relevant Notes human-centric design Notes Highlights If you do a quick search to understand the ROI (return on investment) of focusing on your users, you’ll quickly learn that customer-focused companies can be 60% more profitable than non-customer-focused companies.1 Survey Design Guide: Process, Principles, and Questions | Maze &amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;</description></item><item><title>Hanlon's Razor</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/perdev/kindness/hanlon/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/perdev/kindness/hanlon/</guid><description>Tags: #permanent-notes Relevant Notes design-teams leadership positive-leadership kindness mental-models biases Notes “Never attribute to malice or stupidity that which can be explained by moderately rational individuals following incentives in a complex system of interactions.” Assume the best Highlights How Teams Can Be More Supportive With Help From Hanlon’s Razor 1 “Never attribute to malice or stupidity that which can be explained by moderately rational individuals following incentives in a complex system of interactions.</description></item><item><title>How should we teach?</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/soc-sci/education/how-should-we-teach/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/soc-sci/education/how-should-we-teach/</guid><description> Tags: Relevant Notes Notes Quotes &amp;ldquo;The teacher is of course an artist, but being an artist does not mean that he or she can make the profile, can shape the students. What the educator does in teaching is to make it possible for the students to become themselves.&amp;rdquo; -Paulo Freire Highlights</description></item><item><title>How to Be Stoic</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/philosophy/stoicism/how-to/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/philosophy/stoicism/how-to/</guid><description>Still finding where I got these!
Tags: #philosophy #to-digest Relevant Notes What to answer to mamamatay rin tayong lahat Notes Highlights Dichotomy of Control “The chief task in life is simply this: to identify and separate matters so that I can say clearly to myself which are externals not under my control, and which have to do with the choices I actually control. Where then do I look for good and evil?</description></item><item><title>How to Change Your Life</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/perdev/life-advice/change-life/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/perdev/life-advice/change-life/</guid><description>Tags: #extra-push #to-digest Relevant Notes Notes Highlights Three Steps To Transform Your Life1
From a YT Comment
Step 1. Laser focus on what you want and only what you want. Don&amp;rsquo;t talk yourself or allow yourself to be talked out of your desire. Write it down. Don&amp;rsquo;t let yourself get distracted. Step 2. Question what you consciously and unconsciously believe about your desire. Limiting beliefs prevent us from getting what we desire.</description></item><item><title>InDesign</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/tooling/indesign/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/tooling/indesign/</guid><description>Templates Old Style Newspaper Template - StockInDesign Top 8 Best Free InDesign Templates Sites - Mockups by Carlos Viloria</description></item><item><title>Interviews</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/career/hr/interviews/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/career/hr/interviews/</guid><description> For Leadership in Organizations</description></item><item><title>Interviews for Leaderships in Organizations</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/career/hr/interviews-org/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/career/hr/interviews-org/</guid><description>Tags: #personal-learnings #permanent-notes Relevant Notes Common Questions Tell me about yourself. Why do you want this position? Are you aware of XYZ and its projects? How would you encourage members to join projects/ events? Do you have any projects in mind for the organization? What are your past relevant experience? What will you bring? Tell me about a time you demonstrated leadership skills. What are you most passionate about?</description></item><item><title>Mental Models MOC</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/perdev/ltc/mental-models/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/perdev/ltc/mental-models/</guid><description>#in-progress/garden
Occam&amp;rsquo;s razor OODA loop Levels of magnification Refraction thinking Lindy effect Refraction thinking Hanlon&amp;rsquo;s razor</description></item><item><title>Navigating the Garden</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/home/navigate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/home/navigate/</guid><description>Hello! 👋 Thank you so much for being here! In this page, I map out how this garden is structured for ease of navigation. There are a lot of links &amp;amp; backlinks, so it can get confusing! 😵‍💫
Structure 🏛 Digital gardens are composed of notes that are interlinked for the purpose of linking thinking. As such, there are notes inside notes.
I structured my garden in this manner from when you navigate from the homepage.</description></item><item><title>Never be afraid to ask for help</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/perdev/mh/help/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/perdev/mh/help/</guid><description>Tags: #permanent-notes Relevant Notes life-advice vulnerability Notes There&amp;rsquo;s nothing wrong with asking for help The idea of how some people appear successful/ &amp;ldquo;perfect&amp;rdquo; may create a barrier for them to becoming vulnerable. This prevents them from asking for help and lets them suffer along in private pain. You cannot help others till you learn how to ask yourself. Highlights 7 Cups for the Searching Soul | The 7 Cups Community &amp;ldquo;If you are ashamed of admitting that you have problems, then you cannot ask for help.</description></item><item><title>obsidian</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/tooling/obsidian/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/tooling/obsidian/</guid><description>Helpful Links 100 OBSIDIAN TIPS: Beginner to Advanced in 24 Minutes | Obsidian Tutorial - YouTube Queries in Obsidian Markdown Cheat Sheet | Markdown Guide [Mobile] Setting up iOS git-based syncing with mobile app (using Working Copy) - Share &amp;amp; showcase - Obsidian Forum Will set-up GitHub - blacksmithgu/obsidian-dataview: A complex query language implementation for the Obsidian note-taking tool.</description></item><item><title>On choosing your commitments</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/career/advice/choosing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/career/advice/choosing/</guid><description> Tags: #personal-learnings Relevant Notes Notes It&amp;rsquo;s better to undercommit than overcommit Choose to maximize your impact Strive for quantity &amp;gt; quality Employers look at value of experience, growth, and impact, NOT how many interships you had Highlights</description></item><item><title>On Digital Gardens</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/home/garden/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/home/garden/</guid><description>This digital garden is one of my personal projects this year! I&amp;rsquo;m still learning if there&amp;rsquo;s a proper way of setting it up.
I realized how unconducive for permanence my past notes were. I literally have too much bookmark managers + mind dumps (thanks Apple Notes, Telegram, Messenger, Mem.ai for keeping up with me).
This digital garden serves as my personal knowledge management system. I&amp;rsquo;m a really forgetful person who tends to highlight stuff and tbh rarely comes back to them!</description></item><item><title>On Relating to Others</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/perdev/kindness/relating-to-others/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/perdev/kindness/relating-to-others/</guid><description> Tags: #permanent-notes Relevant Notes learning-thinking-communicating Notes Relating others requires conscious effort and conscious choices. You do not get better at it immediately. Highlights Relating to others is also a process we learn consciously that eventually becomes unconscious.1 7 Cups for the Searching Soul &amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;</description></item><item><title>Personal Knowledge Management</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/productivity/pkm/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/productivity/pkm/</guid><description> Zettelkasten</description></item><item><title>Personality Tests</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/perdev/mh/personality-tests/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/perdev/mh/personality-tests/</guid><description>Tags: #repository #in-progress/garden Relevant Notes Self-awareness Tests My results are here lol. 👻
Enneagram I like the enneagram test because there are a looot of resources about working with enneagram styles as well as the performance of each personality depending on their health level. This is also the test that made me fall in love with personality tests lol.</description></item><item><title>Positive Leadership</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/perdev/leadership/positive-leadership/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/perdev/leadership/positive-leadership/</guid><description> Tags: #in-progress/garden</description></item><item><title>Productivity Systems MOC</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/productivity/productivity-systems-moc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/productivity/productivity-systems-moc/</guid><description>Tags: #in-progress/garden Relevant Notes Systems To-do List Must-do List Must-Should-Want Getting Things Done Zen To Done Pomodoro Technique Time-blocking The Eisenhower Matrix The Moscow Method The Kanban Method Don’t Break the Chain The Daily Trifecta Bullet journalling Seinfeld Calendar System Eat that frog The SMART method MoSCoW method Sources Is there a perfect productivity system?</description></item><item><title>Psychological Safety</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/perdev/mh/psychological-safety/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/perdev/mh/psychological-safety/</guid><description>Tags: #permanent-notes Relevant Notes leadership Notes While there is an idea that creating time for check-ins/ socio-emotional involvement within the team, it&amp;rsquo;s always an investment. Good working environments/ good working cultures foster creativity and good dynamics within the team. Highlights &amp;ldquo;The behaviors that create psychological safety — conversational turn-taking and empathy — are part of the same unwritten rules we often turn to, as individuals, when we need to establish a bond.</description></item><item><title>Public speaking</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/perdev/ltc/public-speaking/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/perdev/ltc/public-speaking/</guid><description>Tags: #permanent-notes Relevant Notes leadership Notes Speak slower and pause more. Create dramatic effect to your speech. Don&amp;rsquo;t eat up your words. Avoid making it scripted and rigid. It&amp;rsquo;s not about formality. Focus on connection. Highlights How to Become a Better Public Speaker When you&amp;rsquo;re public speaking try to speak slower and pause more. Being able to use pauses and own your stage can make your speech a lot more powerful and confident.</description></item><item><title>Quotes on Stoicism</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/philosophy/stoicism/stoic-quotes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/philosophy/stoicism/stoic-quotes/</guid><description>Source: Tags: #philosophy Relevant Notes Thoughts: Quotes “We are often more frightened than hurt; and we suffer more from imagination than from reality.” — Seneca “It’s silly to try to escape other people’s faults. They are inescapable. Just try to escape your own.” —Marcus Aurelius “Our life is what our thoughts make it.” — Marcus Aurelius “If anyone tells you that a certain person speaks ill— of you, do not make excuses about what is said of you but answer, ‘He was ignorant of my other faults, else he would not have mentioned these alone.</description></item><item><title>research</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/soc-sci/education/research/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/soc-sci/education/research/</guid><description> Surveys</description></item><item><title>Research Plan</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/arts-tech/ux-design/research-plan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/arts-tech/ux-design/research-plan/</guid><description>Tags: #permanent-notes Relevant Notes User research Notes Basic plan1
Research objectives Research questions Survey questions and types Survey participants Highlights How to Create and Run an Effective Survey | Maze 1 Research objectives What you’re doing, why you’re doing it, and what you hope to learn Research questions Questions that you’re hoping the research will answer (not what you want surveyees to answer) Survey questions and types Questions you will ask in the survey to help uncover insights about the research questions Survey participants Who are the people you want to survey and why?</description></item><item><title>Roadmap</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/home/roadmap/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/home/roadmap/</guid><description>I have super scrappy baseline knowledge in code. I only reached up to midway of my FreeCodeCamp journey so I&amp;rsquo;m.. lost&amp;hellip;. and reliant on Google search lol. I&amp;rsquo;m documenting my journey here at Building this website. Currently&amp;hellip; Fixing the broken links Fixing the notes tagged #in-progress/garden (also will I ever lol) Concretizing my system 🍃 Revisiting my old notes in Notion, Notes, Mem, Telegram, Messenger, Discord, etc. I really wish I learned about Obsidian earlier grr.</description></item><item><title>Self-awareness</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/perdev/mh/self-awareness/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/perdev/mh/self-awareness/</guid><description>#in-progress/garden</description></item><item><title>Should you send a thank you note?</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/career/hr/ty-note/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/career/hr/ty-note/</guid><description>Tags: #pondering #permanent-notes Relevant Notes career-advice Notes TLDR; Yes. Highlights Thanks or no thanks? Sending a note1
They suggest: Sending a note. Making it handwritten or digital. Making it personal. Showing that you’re interested in the job. Showing that you paid attention to the conversation. Eno Eka I always send a thank you note/ email and I advise my clients to do so because: It is the polite thing to do.</description></item><item><title>Sources on Stoicism</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/philosophy/stoicism/sources-stoicism/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/philosophy/stoicism/sources-stoicism/</guid><description> Tags: #repository #in-progress/garden #come-back Relevant Notes Sources Books The Daily Stoic Podcasts The Daily Stoic Courses Skillshare Stoicism Masterclass</description></item><item><title>Surveys</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/soc-sci/education/research/surveys/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/soc-sci/education/research/surveys/</guid><description>Tags: #permanent-notes Relevant Notes Focus on the user and all else will follow Human-centric design UX design Notes Start with a Research plan Survey design Be inclusive (pronouns!) Make it short &amp;amp; concise Make it consistent Avoid prediction &amp;amp; recall questions Highlights User research Survey Design Guide: Process, Principles, and Questions | Maze 1 When to use surveys To get a sense of user sentiment for an existing product or shortly after launch To gauge interest in a future concept or idea and determine what new products or features should be prioritized To gather demographic information about your users and their needs To dig deeper into a known problem are Scenarios to use During an unmoderated test to gather further feedback to complement your customers’ behavior Follow-up Standalone initiative to gather feedback Creating Create Research plan Align with your team Create the survey Test the survey Launch 🚀 Monitor Survey design principles to keep in mind Align with your stakeholders Set the right expectations with your team Don&amp;rsquo;t miss the pilot test Be intentional Make it valuable Keep it consistent Avoid asking for sensitive information whenever possible Ensure inclusivity Keep things concise Keep it engaging Avoid leading questions and priming Create space for your customers' voice Keep respondents informed Account for order effects Negativity is stronger Prediction and recall are not reliable Avoid asking questions that ask your participant to recall something late in the past or predict their future behavior.</description></item><item><title>The good life is anywhere–you don't have to wait for a certain destination</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/philosophy/stoicism/good-life-is-anywhere/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/philosophy/stoicism/good-life-is-anywhere/</guid><description>Tags: #permanent-notes
Relevant Notes
We often think that happiness should come when we receive xyz or finally get abc, but we shouldn&amp;rsquo;t think of happiness/ a good life as something conditional that happens when we reach a certain point. Instead, we can claim it now.
For reflection “At this moment you aren’t on a journey, but wandering about, being driven from place to place, even though what you seek—to live well—is found in all places.</description></item><item><title>Therapy</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/sciences/psycho/therapy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/sciences/psycho/therapy/</guid><description> Cognitive behavioral therapy</description></item><item><title>Visual Design</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/arts-tech/design/visual/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/arts-tech/design/visual/</guid><description> Tags: #in-progress/garden Relevant Notes Sources A Basic Visual Design Framework #read-queue</description></item><item><title>Vulnerability</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/perdev/life-advice/vulnerability/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/perdev/life-advice/vulnerability/</guid><description>Tags: Relevant Notes Notes Practice vulnerability in your approach. Stay authentic. Highlights Concepts We become closer with people when we’re vulnerable.12 It’s easy for us to think that we’re too selfish, but in fact, most of us aren’t anywhere near selfish enough. We’re not used to putting our own needs, wants, desires centre stage because we’re ‘good’ people.12 Cases Instead of asking “what do you do?</description></item><item><title>We should learn to embrace mediocrity</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/projects/writing/embrace-mediocrity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/projects/writing/embrace-mediocrity/</guid><description>Date: 08052021
Tags: #in-progress/garden #projects Relevant Notes 202108031836 Grounding Why? To break the construct that we should work our ass off in order to achieve societal acceptance To break the social construct that settling is incorrect To impart the concept the it&amp;rsquo;s okay to be mediocre To advocate for prioritizing health over outward sense-seeking How? Share about current societal standards and how it does more harm than good Expose problem of hustle culture Current rates of mental health conditions in PH, especially in working age (if the statistics of this exists!</description></item><item><title>We weren't build to be alone</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/sciences/psycho/not-alone/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/sciences/psycho/not-alone/</guid><description> Tags: #to-digest Relevant Notes collective-effervesence Notes Highlights Psychologists find that in cultures where people pursue happiness individually, they may actually become lonelier. But in cultures where they pursue happiness socially — through connecting, caring and contributing — people appear to be more likely to gain well-being.1 There’s a Specific Kind of Joy We’ve Been Missing &amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;</description></item><item><title>Websites</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/sources/websites/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/sources/websites/</guid><description> Ethics Litmus Tests</description></item><item><title>What to answer to 'mamamatay rin tayong lahat'</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/perdev/life-advice/mamamatay/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/perdev/life-advice/mamamatay/</guid><description>Tags: #personal-learnings Relevant Notes This may seem.. morbid. While I do admit that I sometimes say &amp;ldquo;Mamamatay din tayong lahat&amp;rdquo; in an escapist manner (albeit true), I do acknowledge that it is true, comforting, and a good way to move forward when it comes to handling problems. However, this acceptance into the finite nature of life also makes one prone to not living ceasing each day.
Embracing stoicism is a good way to avoid that mistake.</description></item><item><title>What to Learn</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/perdev/ltc/what-to-learn/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/perdev/ltc/what-to-learn/</guid><description> Tags: #repository Relevant Notes Learning Where to Learn Sources What skills do you recommend I pick up via online courses? - DearTBC</description></item><item><title>When to quit a job?</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/career/advice/quit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/career/advice/quit/</guid><description>Tags: #to-digest Relevant Notes work-culture life-sentence Notes Highlights 15 Warning Signs Your Job Isn&amp;rsquo;t The Right Fit For You1 Job doesn&amp;rsquo;t let you use your strengths Work with manager to explore how to incorporate more of these opportunities in your role Feeling overly negative about work Constantly overwhelmed Lost passion Can&amp;rsquo;t answer &amp;ldquo;what gets you out of bed in the morning?</description></item><item><title>When we have a problem, we tend to go with solutions that involve adding something than taking something existing away</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/sciences/psycho/adding-than-taking/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/sciences/psycho/adding-than-taking/</guid><description>Tags: #permanent-notes Relevant Notes hanlon Notes Highlights When faced with a problem, people tend to select solutions that involve adding new elements rather than taking existing components away.1 The researchers first carried out a set of observational studies, assessments without a control group, to see whether this bias existed at all. In one, they asked 91 participants to make a pattern symmetrical by either adding or removing colored boxes.</description></item><item><title>Where to Learn</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/perdev/ltc/where-to-learn/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/perdev/ltc/where-to-learn/</guid><description> Tags: #in-progress/garden #repository Relevant Notes Learning What to Learn General Courses Skillshare Coursera LinkedIn Learning Udemy FutureLearn Design x Tech Events General Assembly The Gynasium Courses FreeCodeCamp Hyperlink Business GoTo Stage Languages Memrise</description></item><item><title>Work Culture</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/career/hr/work-culture/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/career/hr/work-culture/</guid><description>Tags: #permanent-notes Relevant Notes leadership positive-leadership psychological-safety Notes Good vs bad work culture Good work culture psychological-safety Tools for enhancing connection between team Figma Design Team Trading Cards Highlights Good vs bad work culture Bad work culture Signs company is badly managed1 Employees are fleeing.</description></item><item><title>Workplace equity</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/soc-sci/feminism/workplace-equity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/soc-sci/feminism/workplace-equity/</guid><description>Tags: #permanent-notes #pondering Relevant Notes leadership Notes Distribute tasks between men and women There is a societal expectation for women to volunteer more in non-promotable tasks. This culture holds back women. &amp;ldquo;Not only is their advancement stymied, but also corporations miss out on capturing valuable talent.&amp;quot;1 Managers should take conscious effort into distributing work with equity.</description></item><item><title>Your career is not a life sentence</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/career/advice/life-sentence/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/career/advice/life-sentence/</guid><description>Tags: #permanent-notes Relevant Notes stoicism Notes Highlights &amp;ldquo;We must not get so wrapped up in our work that we think we’re immune from the reality of aging and life. Who wants to be the person who can never let go? Is there so little meaning in your life that your only pursuit is work until you’re eventually carted off in a coffin? Take pride in your work.</description></item><item><title>Zettelkasten</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/productivity/zettelkasten/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/productivity/zettelkasten/</guid><description> Tags: #come-back Relevant Notes Notes Don&amp;rsquo;t fall into the collector&amp;rsquo;s fallacy Highlights</description></item></channel></rss>