<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Notes on</title><link>chloe-garden.live/notes/</link><description>Recent content in Notes on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="chloe-garden.live/notes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>chloe-garden.live/notes/niche/hr/recruitment/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>chloe-garden.live/notes/niche/hr/recruitment/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>chloe-garden.live/notes/permanent-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>chloe-garden.live/notes/permanent-notes/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Check your privilege</title><link>chloe-garden.live/notes/perdev/better/privilege/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>chloe-garden.live/notes/perdev/better/privilege/</guid><description>References
Source: [[The Daily Stoic]] Keywords: permanent notes Tags: Relevant Notes: Becoming Better Thoughts: Quotes “Some people are sharp and others dull; some are raised in a better environment, others in worse, the latter, having inferior habits and nurture, will require more by way of proof and careful instruction to master these teachings and to be formed by them—in the same way that bodies in a bad state must be given a great deal of care when perfect health is sought.</description></item><item><title>How to Be Stoic</title><link>chloe-garden.live/notes/philosophy/stoicism/how-to/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>chloe-garden.live/notes/philosophy/stoicism/how-to/</guid><description>References Source: Keywords: permanent notes Tags: #philosophy #stoicism Relevant Notes: What to answer to mamamatay rin tayong lahat Thoughts: Dichothomy of Control “The chief task in life is simply this: to identify and separate matters so that I can say clearly to myself which are externals not under my control, and which have to do with the choices I actually control. Where then do I look for good and evil?</description></item><item><title>Quotes on Stoicism</title><link>chloe-garden.live/notes/philosophy/stoicism/stoic-quotes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>chloe-garden.live/notes/philosophy/stoicism/stoic-quotes/</guid><description>References Source: Keywords: permanent notes Tags: #stoicism Relevant Notes: Thoughts: Quotes “We are often more frightened than hurt; and we suffer more from imagination than from reality.” — Seneca “It’s silly to try to escape other people’s faults. They are inescapable. Just try to escape your own.” —Marcus Aurelius “Our life is what our thoughts make it.” — Marcus Aurelius “If anyone tells you that a certain person speaks ill— of you, do not make excuses about what is said of you but answer, ‘He was ignorant of my other faults, else he would not have mentioned these alone.</description></item><item><title>Sources</title><link>chloe-garden.live/notes/philosophy/stoicism/sources-stoicism/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>chloe-garden.live/notes/philosophy/stoicism/sources-stoicism/</guid><description>References
Source: Keywords: permanent notes Tags: Relevant Notes: Thoughts: Sources Books The Daily Stoic Podcasts The Daily Stoic Courses Skillshare Stoicism Masterclass</description></item><item><title>What to answer to 'mamamatay rin tayong lahat'</title><link>chloe-garden.live/notes/perdev/mamamatay/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>chloe-garden.live/notes/perdev/mamamatay/</guid><description>This may seem.. morbid. While I do admit that I sometimes say &amp;ldquo;Mamamatay din tayong lahat&amp;rdquo; in an escapist manner (albeit true), I do acknowledge that it is true, comforting, and a good way to move forward when it comes to handling problems. However, this acceptance into the finite nature of life also makes one prone to not living ceasing each day.
Embracing stoicism is a good way to avoid that mistake.</description></item></channel></rss>